

 \times

ag.aditigupta12@gmail.com

+918979798336

in

linkedin.com/in/aditi-gupta-006aab160

SKILLS

ReactJs

HTML

CSS3

JavaScript

Bootstrap

Core Java

Agile & Scrum

Basics of MySQL

Big data with Hadoop

Git

INTERESTS

Travelling

Dancing

Aditi Gupta

Software Developer

Talented individual with strong communication skills, team spirit and with in-depth knowledge of development tools and languages. Seeking for a Software Developer position in a fast growing organization to utilize 1.6+ years of experience in developing designs, test, code and adding value to the organization.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Jr. Associate - ITDaffodil Software

01/2019 – Present

Role/Tasks

Write reusable code to a standard which makes it quick and easy to maintain the code in the future.

Gurugram, India

- Determining the structure and design of web pages.
- Developing features to enhance the user experience.
- Optimize applications for maximum in terms of its speed and scalability.
- Collaborate with back-end developers and web designers to improve usability.

Java Intern Internity Foundation

06/2018 - 06/2018

Role/Tasks

- Contributing in all phases of the development life cycle.
- Writing well-designed, efficient, and testable code.
- Managing Java application development.

PROJECTS

PEEKaMEET - Smart Networking Starts Here (12/2019 – Present)

Developed the full responsive website with a add on feature of Progressive Web App in ReactJS framework.

Firelab Aries (06/2019 – 11/2019)

Created website for fire protection system in ReactJS framework It provides a dashboard for setting up the customers, creating recurring inspections.

Paper Source & Carolina Herrera (04/2019 – 06/2019)

- Created a responsive design for website using HTML, CSS and Bootstrap.
- Integrated Maps and worked on creating reusable components.

EDUCATION

Study Program

Meerut Institute of Engineering and Technology

07/2015 - 04/2019

Courses

 Bachelors of Technology in Computer Science and Engineering

ACHIEVEMENTS

Recieved Challenge Acceptor Award by Internity Foundations for outstanding performance in Java System

Received Microsoft Certification